{
    "id": "bd30e84eb666467a9ed421c41d2db72a",
    "title": "Sentence Completion Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "There is still a glimmer of hope that the strike …………………………….. this week.",
            "description": "The simple future is used to make predictions about the future.",
            "answers": [
                "ends",
                "will end",
                "would end"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "530954c073cc4058b3cdba0cb5c0ff6a"
        },
        {
            "question": "Parents tend to gloss …………………………….. their children’s mistakes.",
            "description": "To gloss over is to excuse or treat lightly.",
            "answers": [
                "out",
                "over",
                "up"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "1d8a8cf421084573a853b44cc6cf2f2e"
        },
        {
            "question": "Be a good winner and don’t gloat ……………………………. your victory.",
            "description": "To gloat over something is to brag about it.",
            "answers": [
                "up",
                "over",
                "out"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "dc00e1eb99574cefb6ec027da04b7a6a"
        },
        {
            "question": "In fairy tales gnomes always …………………………….. hidden treasures.",
            "description": "We use the simple present to talk about facts.",
            "answers": [
                "guard",
                "are guarding",
                "would guard"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "51c67eb794db41a7817f9976e473e155"
        },
        {
            "question": "When something goes wrong, he always makes me the …………………………..",
            "description": "To make someone the goat is to make them the fall guy or the victim.",
            "answers": [
                "goat",
                "sheep",
                "cow"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "7025afda0e374f08ac15e01a6f502c2d"
        },
        {
            "question": "The king’s enemies ………………………….. a rebellion.",
            "description": "To foment is to provoke.",
            "answers": [
                "fomented",
                "fermented",
                "fragmented"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "4346cf9027484f8fa8033e7e23e1ff82"
        },
        {
            "question": "Walking a tightrope ……………………………. the falls was a foolhardy venture.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "across",
                "through",
                "above"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "bd03876db80248929ace90739e98e3ab"
        },
        {
            "question": "You should try to forbear ……………………………. saying such nasty things.",
            "description": "To forebear from is to refrain from.",
            "answers": [
                "to",
                "from",
                "of"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "f06d4f7c1d094a148170a8f49838f1d3"
        },
        {
            "question": "I forbid you …………………………………. out after midnight.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to stay",
                "from staying",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "570af8ee29bc488ebfc13e1a50f90152"
        },
        {
            "question": "The bridge had been built with ……………………………… labor.",
            "description": "Forced labor means enforced labor. ",
            "answers": [
                "forced",
                "forceful"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "854e237b96584dbdb5109e5ff9d25af0"
        },
        {
            "question": "His speech was brief but …………………………..",
            "description": "Forceful means powerful or strong.",
            "answers": [
                "forced",
                "forcible",
                "forceful"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "6c3214ccdb4649f1b986da6e4db96580"
        },
        {
            "question": "The ………………………………… seizure of US sailors by British naval officers was one of the causes of the war of",
            "description": "Forcible means brought about by force.",
            "answers": [
                "forcible",
                "forceful"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "0f89e2225dce4e8482c6ccd4179d70d4"
        }
    ]
}